// dbms

var data = [{
	"question":"Choose the correct option in terms of Issues related to professional responsibility.",
	"a":"Confidentiality",
	"b":"Intellectual property rights",
	"c":"Both Confidentiality & Intellectual property rights",
	"d":"Managing Client Relationships",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Software engineers should not use their technical skills to misuse other people's computers. Here the term misuse refers to:",
	"a":"Unauthorized access to computer material",
	"b":"Unauthorized modification of computer material",
	"c":"Dissemination of viruses or other malware",
	"d":"All of the mentioned",
	"ans":"d"
},{
	"question":"Explain what is meant by PRODUCT with reference to one of the eight principles as per the ACM/IEEE Code of Dbms ?",
	"a":"The product should be easy to use",
	"b":"Software engineers shall ensure that their products and related modifications meet the highest professional standards possible",
	"c":"Software engineers shall ensure that their products and related modifications satisfy the client",
	"d":"It means that the product designed /created should be easily available",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Identify an ethical dilemma from the situations mentioned below:",
	"a":"Your employer releases a safety-critical system without finishing the testing of the system",
	"b":"Refusing to undertake a project",
	"c":"Agreement in principle with the policies of senior management",
	"d":"All of the mentioned",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Identify the correct statement: â€œSoftware engineers shall",
	"a":"act in a manner that is in the best interests of his expertise and favour.",
	"b":"act consistently with the public interest.",
	"c":"ensure that their products only meet the SRS.",
	"d":"all of the mentioned",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Select the incorrect statement: Software engineers should",
	"a":"not knowingly accept work that is outside your competence.",
	"b":"not use your technical skills to misuse other people's computers.",
	"c":"be dependent on their colleagues.",
	"d":"maintain integrity and independence in their professional judgment.",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Efficiency in a software product does not include ________",
	"a":"responsiveness",
	"b":"licensing",
	"c":"memory utilization",
	"d":"processing time",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Running other software on idle computer without the knowledge of the organization is called theft of ____",
	"a":"Software",
	"b":"Computer",
	"c":"Computer time",
	"d":"Use",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"The reason for software bugs and failures is due to",
	"a":"Software companies",
	"b":"Software Developers",
	"c":"Both Software companies and Developers",
	"d":"All of the mentioned",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Company has latest computers and state-of the- art software tools, so we shouldn't worry about the quality of the product.",
	"a":" True",
	"b":"False",
	"ans":"b"
}];